humanworkplace.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy – Human Workplace

—-

Like most website operators, Human Workplace collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Human Workplace’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Human Workplace’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Human Workplace may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Human Workplace also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://humanworkplace.com blogs/sites. Human Workplace only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

##  **SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?**

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

##  **SECTION 2 – CONSENT**

###  **How do you get my consent?**

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, opt in to receive coupons, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

###  **How do I withdraw my consent?**

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at support@humanworkplace.com.

###  **How will you contact me?  **

We reserve the right to contact our customers via outbound email in order to resolve customer service situations. This is including, but not limited to claims, fraud, and solving other customer issues.

##  **SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

##  **SECTION 4 –  ECOMMERCE**

Our store is hosted on private servers. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through our data storage, databases and the general application.

They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

###  **Payment:**

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, we do not store your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

##  **SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

##  **SECTION 6 – PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Human Workplace discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Human Workplace’s behalf or to provide services available at Human Workplace’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Human Workplace’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Human Workplace will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Human Workplace discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Human Workplace believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Human Workplace,  third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a Human Workplace website and have supplied your email address, Human Workplace may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Human Workplace and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Human Workplace takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

###  **Links**

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

##  **SECTION 7 – SECURITY**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

##  **SECTION 8 – AGGREGATED STATISTICS**

Human Workplace may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Human Workplace may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Human Workplace does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

##  **SECTION 9 – ADS**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Human Workplace and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

##  **SECTION 10 – COOKIES**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Human Workplace uses cookies to help Human Workplace identify and track visitors, their usage of Human Workplace website, and their website access preferences. Human Workplace visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Human Workplace’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Human Workplace’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

  * PHPSESSID – PHP Session ID
  * __cfduid
  * _ga – Google analytics ID
  * _gat – Google analytics property ID
  * _gid – Google unique identifier
  * pys_fb_pixel_traffic_source – Facebook marketing pixel traffic source ID
  * tl_130109_130111_3 – Popup for Catalog
  * tl_130127_130127_4 – Popup for Catalog
  * tve_leads_unique – Leads generator unique session
  * wfvt_3963654799 – Wordfence protection to identify session
  * wordfence_verifiedHuman – Wordfence protection to identify malicious bot users
  * wp_woocommerce_session_f462cf67b92e12890d677af15d5340f9 – Woocommerce Session ID to save cart

 **The Facebook Pixel**  is used for Facebook Ads and Facebook Analytics. It does use private data and you will need to ask for prior consent. Facebook has also implemented flexible ways for their users to see and control how the pixel is used on partner websites. Inform your users about their rights and available options.  **Each Facebook user can control their ad settings from here:  <https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen>**

Under  **“Advertisers you’ve interacted with”**  there is a tab named  **“Whose website or app you’ve used”**  where you can review advertisers whose ads you may be seeing currently because you visited their website or app that uses Facebook technology. That’s basically the data sent by the Facebook Pixel.

##  **SECTION 11 – AGE OF CONSENT**

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

##  **SECTION 12 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

If Human Workplace, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Human Workplace goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Human Workplace may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Human Workplace may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Human Workplace’s sole discretion. Human Workplace encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a https://humanworkplace.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

##  **QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at support@humanworkplace.com
